Finding Aid for the Theodore Bikel Papers LSC.2321
UCLA Library Special Collections
- Series 6: Audiovisual material, 1957-2014
  Series contains an assortment of film, video and audio materials, including audiotapes from Bikel's radio shows.
  CONTAINS UNPROCESSED AUDIO AND AUDIOVISUAL MATERIALS: Audio and audiovisual materials are not currently available for access and will require further processing and assessment. If you have questions about this material please email spec-coll@library.ucla.edu.
  - Bikel at Home, undated (Box 232-233)
    There are 14 1/4 inch audiotapes, labeled "Bikel at Home."
    CONTAINS UNPROCESSED AUDIOVISUAL MATERIALS: Audiovisual materials are not currently available for access and will require further processing and assessment. If you have questions about this material please email spec-coll@library.ucla.edu.
  - Bickle, 1959 April 5 (Box 234)
    There are three 1/4 inch audiotapes, labeled "Bickle, April 5, 1959."
  - Theo - Rough Cut, undated (Box 234)
    There are three 1/4 inch audiotapes, labeled "Theo #1-3, Rough Cut."
  - Bikel on "Tex & Jinx", undated (Box 234)
    There is one 1/4 inch audiotape, labeled "Bikel on "Tex & Jinx"."
  - Gate of Horn, 1957 January 26 (Box 235)
    There are two 1/4 inch audiotapes, labeled "Gate of Horn."
  - Shepherd, 1961 April 29 (Box 235)
    There are two 1/4 inch audiotapes, labeled "Shepherd."
  - Colpix, undated (Box 235)
    There is one 1/4 inch audiotape, labeled "Colpix master copy."
  - Hadassah Anniversary, undated (Box 235)
    There is one 1/4 inch audiotape, labeled "Hadassah Anniversary."
  - Russian Selections, undated (Box 235)
    There is one 1/4 inch audiotape, labeled "Russian Selections."
  - Bikel Extras, undated (Box 236)
    There are two 1/4 inch audiotapes, labeled "Bikel extras."
  - Sat 2-1, undated (Box 236)
    There is one 1/4 inch audiotape, labeled "Sat 2-1."
  - Unlabeled audiotape, 1961 March 12 (Box 236)
    There is one 1/4 inch audiotape, labeled with just the date "3-12-61."
  - Syracuse Symposium, 2003 March 17 (Box 236)
    There are two 1/4 inch videotapes, labeled "Syracuse Symposium."
  - Peacekeepers, undated (Box 236)
    There are four 1/4 inch audiocassettes in a box, labeled "Peacekeepers."
  - Mortal Sins, undated (Box 236)
    There are four 1/4 inch audiocassettes in a box, labeled "Mortal Sins."
  - Bikel, undated (Box 236)
    There are five 1/4 inch audiotapes, labeled "Bikel."
  - Star on Walk of Fame, undated (Box 237)
    There is one 1/4 inch audiocassette, labeled "Star on Walk of Fame."
  - Dress Rehearsal for Bonner & Moore Pres., 1983 January 18 (Box 237)
    There is one U-matic, labeled "Dress Rehearsal for Bonner & Moore Pres."
  - Unlabeled videotapes, undated (Box 237)
    There are two unlabeled U-matics.
  - Unlabeled audiotape, undated (Box 237)
    There is one unlabeled 1/4 inch audiotape.
  - Hitchcock + Twilight Zone, undated (Box 237)
    There is one VHS labeled "Hitchcock + Twilight Zone."
  - Theodore Bikel - In the Shoes of Sholom Aleichem, 2014 (Box 237)
    There is one CD labeled "Theodore Bikel - In the Shoes of Sholom Aleichem."
  - Walk of Fame - Funeral Excerpt, 2005 April 29 (Box 237)
    There is one CD labeled "Walk of Fame- Funeral Excerpt."
  - Theodore Bikel - A Mighty Day, undated (Box 237)
    There is one CD labeled "Theodore Bikel - A Mighty Day."
  - Ed Sullivan, undated (Box 238)
    There are two 16mm films labeled "Ed Sullivan."
  - Out of Bondage, 1974 (Box 238)
    There is one 16mm film labeled "Out of Bondage."
  - Future Tech...From Technion, undated (Box 238)
    There is one 16mm film labeled "Future Tech...From Technion."
  - Dog of Flanders, undated (Box 238)
    There are two 16mm films labeled "Dog of Flanders."
  - Greece, Zurich, Petticoat Lane, undated (Box 238)
    There is one 16mm film labeled "Greece, Zurich, Petticoat Lane."
  - Israel & Spain, undated (Box 238)
    There is one 16mm film labeled "Israel & Spain."
  - Greece, Hyde Park, Paris, undated (Box 238)
    There is one 16mm film labeled "Greece, Hyde Park, Paris."
  - 16 mm film, undated (Box 294)
    THIS BOX CONTAINS UNPROCESSED AUDIO/AUDIOVISUAL MATERIALS: Audio/audiovisual materials are not currently available for access and will require further processing and assessment. If you have questions about this material please email spec-coll@library.ucla.edu.
  - The African Queen 16 mm film, 1951 (Box 295)
  - The African Queen 16 mm film, 1951 (Box 296)
  - The Prison 16 mm film, 1962 (Box 297)
  - Pericles on 31st Street 16 mm film, 1962 (Box 298)
  - The United States Steel Hour 16 mm film, 1955-1956 (Box 299)
  - Pat Boone Chevy Showroom 16 mm film, 1960 (Box 300)
  - CBS 16 mm film, undated (Box 301)
  - Look Up and Live 16 mm film (Box 302)
  - The Perry Como Show 16 mm film, undated (Box 303)
  - Frontiers of Faith: Shall These Bones Live 16 mm film, 1959 (Box 304)
  - Frontiers of Faith: Oil For But One Day 16 mm film, 1959 (Box 305)